Heavy Knight
As a result
Episode 1\h\h\h\h\hElymas the Heavy Knight
Doppellusion
Baptisma
Elymas Edvaughn
Attack
Defense
Magic
Speed
Equipment
Skills
Class Heavy Knight
Elymas Edvaughn
Attack
Defense
Baptisma
Class: Master Swordsman
Malice Edvaughn
Elymas Edvaughn
Attack
Defense
Magic
Skill Tree: Heavy Knight
Skill Points Remaining
Oath of the Heavy Armor
Defense Booster
Beginner Swordsmanship
Skill Tree: Heavy Knight
Skill Points Remaining
Oath of the Heavy Armor
Defense Booster
Beginner Swordsmanship
Skill Tree
\h\hSkill Tree: Heavy Knight
Skill Points Remaining
\h\h\hOath of the Heavy Armor
\hDefense Booster
Beginner Swordsmanship
\h\hSkill Tree: Heavy Knight
Skill Points Remaining
Oath of the Heavy Armor
Fixed Skills
Random Skills
Oath of the Heavy Armor
Defense Booster
Beginner Swordsmanship
HA HA HA HA HA
Beginner
Swordsmanship
Advanced
Skill Tree: Heavy Knight
Skill Points Remaining
Oath of the Heavy Armor
Defense Booster
\hBeginner Swordsmanship
5 skill points assigned to Oath of the Heavy Knight
Oath of the Heavy Armor has reached level 2
Rampart Reflection skill has been acquired
Oath of the Heavy Armor has reached level 5
Defense has increased by 10
Elymas Edvaughn
Attack
Defense
Magic
Speed
Equipment
Grunt Sword
Iron Armor
Skills
Rampart Reflection
Monster:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRaana
Monster:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRaana
Rampart
Reflection
Rampart Reflection
Common Skill
m 0 0 l 290 0 290 42 0 42
When an enemy melee attack is negated,
deal damage equal to the user's Defense
Defense
I'm Elymas
the Heavy Knight.